Contact

dsellison91@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/deborahellison-ba154273 (LinkedIn) www.weebly.com/weebly/main.php (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Management
Hospital Administration
Healthcare Management

Certifications
Certified Emergency Nurse
CEN

Deborah Ellison

Registered Nurse at Kaiser Permanente

Greater Seattle Area

Summary

I have had a broad range of nursing and leadership experience. I work collaboratively with interdisciplinary professionals toward a goal of providing an excellent patient care experience. I have completed a master's degree in nursing. Strengths: critical thinking, problem solving, team orientation, superb written and verbal communication skills.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse December 2019 - Present (8 months) Greater Seattle Area

EvergreenHealth
Registered Nurse
November 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Kirkland, Washington

Working within the Float Pool team to provide nursing care to patients and families within the Kirkland Evergreen facility. Areas covered while floating include Medical, Surgical, Oncology, Orthopedics and Acute Rehabilitation, Telemetry and Hospice. Experience with Cerner computer systems. Served as a mentor to senior practicum student. Provided care to a patient involved in an active research study.

Swedish Medical Center 20 years

RN

December 1996 - November 2016 (20 years) Edmonds. WA

I worked in the float pool performing jobs throughout the hospital in areas wherever the need. I have worked in departments including, the emergency room, medical/surgical, telemetry and the psychiatric units. I have critical care

experience and have worked as a rapid response RN, nursing supervisor, and as an interim manager.

Interim Manager

February 2014 - April 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Edmonds. WA

Gained experience as an interim manager of busy, 34 bed medical / orthopedic unit, float pool and IV team. Responsible for day to day operations, budgeting, planning and staffing. Focused on staff development and a commitment to providing an excellent patient experience. Maintained alignment with organizational mission, vision, values and strategic plan.

Saint Alphonsus Regional Medical Center

RN

May 1995 - August 1996 (1 year 4 months)

Boise, Idaho Area

Worked as a registered nurse in a medical oncology unit. Learned basic nursing skills, such as time management, prioritization of care, application of the nursing process and communication with patients and their families. Also developed nursing care skills such as: central line and other IV management, feeding tubes, dressing changes, and urinary drain management.

Education

University of Washington

Master's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (2013 - 2015)

University of Hawaii at Manoa

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1990 - 1994)